<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Defacto Matter</title>
    <link>https://alonzoc1.github.io/planet-reborn-hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Defacto Matter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://alonzoc1.github.io/planet-reborn-hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://alonzoc1.github.io/planet-reborn-hugo/demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alonzoc1.github.io/planet-reborn-hugo/demo/</guid>
      <description>Demo Resources Link to heading Downloads Link to heading Windows Mac Code Link to heading Our codebase is available for viewing on GitHub!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://alonzoc1.github.io/planet-reborn-hugo/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alonzoc1.github.io/planet-reborn-hugo/overview/</guid>
      <description>Game Overview Link to heading What is Planet Reborn all about? Link to heading Planet Reborn is a third-person action roguelike game, where the player must overcome overwhelming odds stacked against them. You will have to scavenge items that will aid your escape from the planet, gain new abilities, and fight your way past powerful enemies.
Find out more about Planet Reborn by reading our Game Design Document here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://alonzoc1.github.io/planet-reborn-hugo/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alonzoc1.github.io/planet-reborn-hugo/about/</guid>
      <description>#Who Are We? Info Here at Defacto Matter, we have a strong development foundation and we strive to do our best. We are strong team of four developers who have been cultivating an environment of creativity and innovation. Our mission is to create Planet Reborn and make it as our flagship title!
#Our Unique History Defacto Matter strives to work towards great games that focus on the gamer over shady market practices, which is why the four founding members were formerly developers of GreedyGames LLC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://alonzoc1.github.io/planet-reborn-hugo/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alonzoc1.github.io/planet-reborn-hugo/blog/</guid>
      <description>Why did we make Planet Reborn? Link to heading We wanted to create this game, because we wanted to make a game that&amp;rsquo;s similar to Risk of Rain, but with our own spin to it. In addition, our development team particularly enjoys Roguelike games. Therefore, we set upon creating Planet Reborn as a sci-fi roguelike game. We titled our game Planet Reborn to represent our philosophy of what today&amp;rsquo;s games should be like: a simple free game that does not try to insert any microtransactions or pay-to-win elements and instead simply focuses on delivering a good game.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
